RAHUL KUMAR JHAMTANI

Phone: (+91)-72209-88840

E-mail: rahulkumarjhamtani@gmail.com

Website: rahulkumarjhamtani.github.io

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

PROFILE .

I'm a 21 year old web designer and developer with a focus on new technology, content, and layout design. I want to work across the full stack of Software Development. I've built a few projects by myself and I'm looking for a role where I can grow and learn from other experienced team members and my friends.

EXPERIENCE

WEB DESIGNER

Tribal Connect (2021 - present)

- Direct software design
- Evaluate interface between hardware and software
- Lead in the design, development, and implementation of the graphic, layout, production and communication.

WEB DESIGNER & PRESENTER

Vedik Cyber Forces (2020 - present)

- Won STH-21
- Front-end developer and project manager
- Prepared presentations and reports

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS and JS
- SQL
- C/C++
- Communication

HOBBIES

Playing cricket, Watching movies and listening songs

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

Anand ICE (2019-present)

PRIMARY & SECONDARY SCHOOLING

Maheshwari Public School (2007 - 2019)